<localization>
  <metrics>
    <metric abbrv="DEBUG" label="No metrics selected">
      No metric was selected.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="TP"  label="True positive">
      The test method correctly predicted a positive result.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="TN"  label="True negative">
      The test method correctly predicted a negative result.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="FN"  label="False negative">
      The test method wrongly predicted a negative result. It is actually positive. (Also: Type II error)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="FP"  label="False positive">
      The test method wrongly predicted a positive result. It is actually negative. (Also: Type I error)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="P"   label="condition positive">
      The number of real positive cases in the data.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="N"   label="condition negative">
      The number of real negative cases in the data.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="prevalence" label="prevalence">
      The proportion of positive results in the total population (measured samples).
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="TPR" label="sensitivity">
      The proportion of positives that are correctly identified. (Also: recall, hit rate, or true positive rate)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="TNR" label="specificity">
      The proportion of negatives that are correctly identified. (Also: selectivity or true negative rate)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="PPV" label="positive predictive value">
      The proportions of positive and negative results that are positive. (Also: precision)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="NPV" label="negative predictive value">
      The proportions of positive and negative results that are negative.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="FNR" label="false negative rate">
      The proportion of positives that are falsly identified as negative. (Also: miss rate)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="FPR" label="false positive rate">
      The proportion of negatives that are falsly identified as positive. (Also: fall-out)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="FDR" label="false discovery rate">
      The propotion of positives calls that are actually false positive.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="FOR" label="false omission rate">
      The propotion of negative calls that are actually false negative.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="ACC" label="accuracy">
      The propotion of correctly identified results.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="F1"  label="F1 score">
      The F1 score is the harmonic mean of positive predictive value and sensitivity.
      The highest possible value of an F-score is 1, 
      indicating perfect precision and recall, 
      and the lowest possible value is 0, 
      if either the precision or the recall is zero.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="MCC" label="Matthews correlation coefficient">
      A correlation coefficient between the reference and test results.
      It returns a value between -1 and +1. 
      A coefficient of +1 represents a perfect prediction,
      0 no better than random prediction
      and -1 indicates total disagreement between reference and test results.
      (Also: phi coefficient)
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="LR+" label="positive likelihood ratio">
      The probability of a person who has the disease testing positive divided
      by the probability of a person who does not have the disease testing positive.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="LR-" label="negative likelihood ratio">
      The probability of a person who has the disease testing negative divided 
      by the probability of a person who does not have the disease testing negative.
    </metric>
    <metric abbrv="CK" label="Cohen's kappa (κ)">
      If the raters are in complete agreement then k = 1.
      If there is no agreement among the raters other than what would be expected by chance, k = 0.
      If the kappa is negative, the aggrement is worse than random. (Switch the labels...)
    </metric>
  </metrics>
</localization>